Kyu Hur

(080) 4681-3442 **♦** kyuhur2@gmail.com **♦** Tokyo, Japan

SUMMARY

I am a software engineer with degrees from the **University of Tokyo** and the **University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign**. With a history of diverse educational pursuits and experiences, I provide crucial technical and business perspectives in the realm of technology.

I have **one year** of professional software engineering experience, **three years** of leadership and project management experience, and **five years** of general research experience.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

OS Windows, Linux, WSL

Languages (Software) Python, R, SQL, Java, Svelte

Languages (Linguistic) English (Native), Korean (Fluent), Japanese (Conversational)

Platforms Azure
Tools Git, UML

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Feb 2021 – Present

FPT Software Tokyo, Japan

- Develop and optimize time-series demand forecasting models, producing 5~10% more accurate forecasts and saving a projected USD\$100,000 a year for a client over the next 3 years
- Establish standardized systems for projects using pre-commit, code formatting tools, and code linting tools, saving approximately eighty man-hours per project
- Perform coding reviews, write unit tests, and integrate new models as part of the broader machine learning DevOps team
- Deliver monthly presentations our end-to-end forecasting SaaS product to clients and external team members in Japan, South Korea, Malaysia, Germany, and the United States
- Oversee weekly duties and goals of three data science interns and junior data scientists

Research Intern Nov 2021 – Present

Stanford University

Remote

- Develop novel data accessibility and data security rating systems of popular wearable devices
 (e.g. Fitbit, Apple Watch) used for clinical trials
- Draft a chapter of a comprehensive manuscript discussing the role of wearable devices in health research, slated for publication in Lancet Digital Health

Medical Affairs Intern Apr 2020 – Dec 2020

Janssen Pharmaceutical Companies of Johnson & Johnson

Tokyo, Japan

- Spearheaded a three-member team project to determine that Macitentan was prescribed twice as frequent as a competitor's and had fewer side effects
- Produced reports on the effectiveness of a new schizophrenia therapy in Japan

Graduate Research and Teaching Assistant

Jul 2020 - Oct 2020

University of Tokyo Tokyo, Japan

 Teaching Assistant for the "Environmental Health and Research Methods" course taught by Dr. Yoonhee Kim

Trained and managed three other graduate and undergraduate students

Academic Researcher

Mar 2016 - Dec 2018

University of Illinois

Illinois, USA

- Co-author of three academic publications pertaining to water engineering technology
- Trained two new undergraduate and graduate hires to perform various laboratory experiments
- Collaborated with three postdoctoral scholars to meet the short-term goals of active grants
- Analyzed lethal dose levels of water sources for multiple, million-dollar grants awarded by the National Institute of Health, National Science Foundation, and the United States Department of Defense

PROJECTS

Benchmarking Tool

FPT Software

 Develop a close-sourced tool to benchmark models on custom datasets against state-of-the-art models under Amazon's GluonTS Python package

Wearipedia Stanford University

- Build and contribute to sections of over 20 wearable devices on the market
- Written in Svelte with Prismic, available at wearipedia.org

Air Pollution, Pollen, and Mortality Correlation

University of Tokyo

Graduated: Mar 2021

Graduated: May 2018

 Determined an exacerbating effect of pollen on air pollution and mortality in nine cities in Japan with R and Python. Published in the 2021 ISEE conference

Personal Website

- Created a personal website detailing work experience and passion projects
- Written in Ruby and SCSS, available at kyuhur2.github.io

EDUCATION

University of Tokyo

Master of Science in Health Science

University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign

Bachelor of Science in Liberal Arts and Science, Chemistry